Information
>> [music]
>> is not transformation. You're not
confused about what needs to be done
next. You're avoiding it. So, I think we
convinced ourselves that collecting
information [music] meant healing.
Another birth chart, Ayurvedic this
time, another book, another sage.
Believe you me, I love this
Information is not transformation.
[music]
Stay with it for a minute. Knowing your
attachment style, knowing your childhood
wounds, knowing your purpose is not
transformation. Transformation is making
the phone call to apologize, leaving the
relationship to protect [music] your
peace, starting the business even though
your family said it failed miserably,
going for the [music] run that you
hate, quitting the job you know
you weren't meant for. Transformation is
[music] action. The funny thing about
healing is you don't find all the
answers and then begin. You just
do it. You just start without a clue,
just begin. [music] And then, after you
begin, life starts showing you what
really still needs to be worked on. You
think you healed your anger until
somebody cuts you off in traffic and you
follow him for 27 blocks until you
finally catch up to him and threaten to
bite off their finger if they ever flip
you off again. You think you've healed
your fear until it's time to bet on
yourself. The trigger [music]
isn't the problem. The trigger is the
flashlight. Stop waiting until you're
certain. Certainty is a fairy tale they
sell you because uncertainty is
uncomfortable. Real life gut instincts,
educated guesses, bad decisions, course
corrections, and a whole lot of figuring
it out as you go. The reality is
nobody's coming to tell you it's going
to be okay. If you listen to absolutely
nothing else I say, I want you to listen
to this one thing.
>> [music]
>> Trust your feet. That's it. Trust your
feet. The two feet you have on the
bottom of your legs, trust those. The
path doesn't begin before you move. The
path is made by you moving your feet.
[music] Stop asking the universe for
another sign to move. The
synchronicities are there. That bird
that landed on that branch that you
swore up and down stared straight into
your soul,
sign. The deja vu, the same number you
keep seeing on repeat, the fact that you
can't stop thinking about it is the
sign. They're all signs. Trust your
feet.